In the next several videos we're going to apply what we've learned in the class to
在接下来的几个视频中，我们将把我们在课堂上学到的知识应用到
analysis of various features of Java. This will give us a chance to both look at a
分析了Java的各种特性。这将给我们一个机会，让我们既能看到
real programming language and how it's designed and been done. And also to talk
真正的编程语言，以及它是如何设计和实现的。也是为了谈论
about some features that art in Cool that we haven't been able to cover thus far in
关于Cool中的一些艺术特性，我们到目前为止还没有在
the course. For the perspective of this class, Java is a kind of Cool on steroids.
这门课。从这个类的角度来看，Java是一种对类固醇的冷静。
It's Cool plus more features, many more features. At, at their core Java and Cool
这是很酷的，加上更多的功能，更多的功能。At，其核心是Java和Cool
are very similar. Java and Cool are both typed object oriented garbage collected
是非常相似的。Java和Cool都是面向对象的类型化垃圾回收
languages. They were both designed in the early 1990s and so they share a common
语言。它们都是在20世纪90年代初设计的，因此它们有一个共同之处
culture there with the ideas that were current at that time. So in this video,
那里的文化带有当时流行的思想。所以在这段视频中，
I'm just going to give a little bit of history of Java so that will be the focus
我只想简单介绍一下Java的历史，这将是重点
really of this rather short video. And then in the subsequent videos, we'll talk
这段相当短的视频真的很精彩。然后在接下来的视频中，我们将谈论
about all the features or some of the features of Java that are not in Cool. And
关于Java的所有特性或一些不太酷的特性。和
we'll use the ideas of course that we've been discussing all along through the
当然，我们将使用我们一直在讨论的想法
class, to explain a little bit about those ideas. But I think these are all important
同学们，来解释一下这些想法。但我认为这些都很重要
language constructs that are unfortunately were too time consuming or too complicated
不幸的是，语言构造太耗时或太复杂
to add to the course project. So I think it's useful to use a language like
要添加到课程项目中。所以我认为使用像这样的语言是有用的
[inaudible] to illustrate how these ideas work and what some of the issues are. So
[听不见]来说明这些想法是如何运作的，以及其中的一些问题是什么。所以
Java began as a project called Oak at SUN Microsystems and it was originally
Java最初是SUN Microsystems的一个名为Oak的项目，最初是
targeted at set top devices. And so what was a set top device? This was a little
目标是机顶盒设备。那么什么是机顶盒设备呢？这是一个小小的
box that was gonna sit on top of your TV So you had your TV screen, and then there
这个盒子会放在你的电视上，这样你就有了电视屏幕，然后就在那里
was going to be this little thing up here that was going to sit on top of the TV
这上面会有一个小东西，它会坐在电视顶上
that was going to control all your cable programming. So this would essentially
它会控制你所有的有线电视节目。所以这基本上会
would connect to some kind of network and it would help you to do, you know to make
会连接到某种网络，这会帮助你做，你知道要做的事
your TV more interactive. Okay, so this was back in the days before every TV was
让您的电视更具互动性。好的，这是在每一台电视还没有出现之前的日子里
really a computer by itself. The initial develo pment of, of Oak took several
实际上它本身就是一台电脑。橡树的最初开发花了几个月的时间。
years. I believe the project ran from about 91 to 94 and what happened, at least
几年了。我相信这个项目大约从91年持续到94年，至少发生了什么
as I understand it, is that this set top device market just never took off. So this
据我所知，这个机顶盒市场从来没有起飞过。所以这件事
never became a popular never, never became a popular idea with consumers and, and so
从来没有成为一个流行的，从来没有成为消费者欢迎的想法，所以
there really was a kind of limited up side or a limited potential for, for Oak at the
对于奥克来说，确实有一种有限的上行空间或有限的潜力
time. And then something happened, the Internet happened. So also in the early
时间到了。然后发生了一些事情，互联网发生了。同样在早期也是如此
90s the Internet revolution was really gathering steam. Everybody was getting on
90年代的互联网革命确实愈演愈烈。每个人都上了车
the Internet and it became obvious sometime 93, 94 that there was going to be
互联网，很明显在93，94年的某个时候，将会有
a need for programming languages that really addressed these specific issues on
需要能够真正解决这些特定问题的编程语言
the Internet. And in particular people were very concerned about security. And,
互联网。尤其是人们非常关心安全问题。和,
they didn't want to be downloading lots of binaries that were programs written in C
他们不想下载很多用C编写的二进制程序
and passing those around on the Internet because it was just really no guarantee
并在互联网上传播这些信息，因为这真的不能保证
that those programs would work as intended and not crash your machine. So you know,
这些程序将按预期工作，而不会使您的机器崩溃。所以你知道，
they needed to be able to share code over the Internet from other people that you
他们需要能够通过Internet与其他人共享代码，
didn't necessarily trust completely meant that we needed safer languages than
不一定完全信任意味着我们需要比
languages like C and C++ and so there was an opportunity there for a, a new language
像C和C++这样的语言，所以那里有一种，一种新的语言的机会
and there were several candidates actually. Besides Java, Tickle and Python
实际上有几个候选人。除了Java、Tickle和Python
were very serious candidates to become the Internet programming language eventually
我们都是非常认真的候选人，最终会成为互联网编程语言
the backing of SUN Microsystems, the backing of SUN gave to Java helped it to
SUN Microsystems的支持，SUN给予Java的支持帮助它
really gain a very, very strong presence on the Internet. But you know, the point
在互联网上真的获得了非常非常强大的影响力。但你知道，重点是
of this story is that every new language needs a killer app. Every programming
这个故事的核心是，每一种新语言都需要一个杀手级的应用程序。每一个节目
language rides into the world on the back of some application. So there has to be
语言是在一些应用程序的支持下进入这个世界的。所以一定会有
some kind of new application that people want to write that the existing languages
人们想要编写的某种新的应用程序，即现有的语言
don't serve very well and that provides the opportunity and therefore makes it
发球不是很好，这提供了机会，因此使它
worthwhile for people to learn a new programming language. And so the fact that
对于人们来说，学习一门新的编程语言是值得的。所以事实是
Ja va was a very safe language, it had the garbage collection. It had the type system
JAVA是一种非常安全的语言，它有垃圾收集功能。它有类型系统
that made it well suited at the time to the, the needs of the emerging needs of
这使得它在当时很好地适应了新兴需求的需要
internet programming. And it became very popular I think primarily because of that
互联网编程。它变得非常受欢迎，我认为主要是因为
reason. And if you if you recall there was a lecture or a video early on, on the
原因。如果你还记得早些时候有一场讲座或一段视频，在
economy of programming languages. And I would recommend actually that if you
编程语言的经济性。实际上我会建议如果你
haven't watched that one, then you go back and take a look because there I discuss
我没看过那部，那你回去看看吧，因为我在那里讨论过
some of these ideas about how languages are adopted in more detail. So Java also
其中一些关于语言如何被采用的想法更加详细。所以Java也是
came into existence in a particular technical environment and it's very
它是在特定的技术环境中产生的，它非常
common. In fact, it's normal for new programming languages to borrow heavily
很普通。事实上，新的编程语言大量借用是很正常的
from their predecessors and new languages are often mostly recombinations of ideas
来自它们的前辈和新的语言通常是思想的重新组合
from previous languages in a new design perhaps with some innovations thrown in.
在一个新的设计中使用以前的语言，也许还加入了一些创新。
And the particular influences on Java. Again this is at least so far as I
以及它对Java的特殊影响。再说一次，至少到目前为止我
understand it so the type system in Java, or its, its commitment to types probably
了解它，可能是因为Java中的类型系统，或者它对类型的承诺
is traceable to Modula-3 and the ideas there where people try to build a sort of
可以追溯到模3和那里的想法，在那里人们试图建立一种
programming language that would scale in a realistic way to large systems but also be
一种编程语言，它将以一种现实的方式扩展到大型系统，但同时也
strongly typed. The object orientation of Java is traceable to languages like
强类型。Java的面向对象可以追溯到像这样的语言
Objective C and C++ and, and also Eiffel which also had the idea of interfaces
目标C和C++，还有同样具有接口思想的Eiffel
which is a prominent feature in Java. And finally Java is quite a dynamic language
这是Java中的一个突出特性。最后，Java是一种非常动态的语言
meaning that there many things that are not done staticly. They're done
这意味着有很多事情不是静态地做的。他们做完了
dynamically so features like reflection would be one example of that. And there
动态的，所以像反射这样的功能就是一个例子。还有那里
are actually quite a few other features and there is some history there. There's
实际上还有相当多的其他功能，而且那里有一些历史。那里有
some shared culture there with Lisp. This was a or is a functional family language
在那里和Lisp有一些共同的文化。这是一种或现在是一种实用的家庭语言
but is also a very, very dynamic language. As I said at the beginning this video is
但也是一种非常非常有活力的语言。正如我在开头所说的，这个视频是
just an introduction and overview and in the next few videos, we'll be looking at
这只是一个介绍和概述，在接下来的几个视频中，我们将看到
specific features of Java and how they work. And that will includes things like
Java的特定功能及其工作方式。这份遗嘱包括像这样的东西
exceptions, interfaces, and threads. As well as a bunch of other features that
异常、接口和线程。以及一系列其他功能，这些功能
we'll discuss at least, briefly. One thing to realize is that Java is a big language.
我们将至少简短地讨论一下。需要认识到的一件事是Java是一种很大的语言。
It is not simple. The language manual for Java runs to hundreds and hundreds of
这并不简单。Java的语言手册有成百上千的
pages. It has lots of features. And perhaps more importantly, lots of feature
佩奇。它有很多特点。也许更重要的是，很多功能
interactions. So. The hard part of designing a language of course is getting
互动。所以。当然，设计一门语言最难的部分是
all the feature interactions right. All the combinations of the features and, you
所有功能交互都是正确的。所有功能和您的组合
know making sure there are no surprising interactions between them.
要知道，要确保他们之间没有令人惊讶的互动。